Get out of my house!
We'll talk later.
Where's Mark, Debbie?
I know you're a superhero.
Fly away, flyboy.
Hey, Eve.
So I'm helping you today.
We've been
growing you a new body.
Does Mark know
that his dad's a murderer?
Keep out of this, Cecil.
It's Mark's mom.
I need to talk to him.
What's going on?
Where's Omni-Man?
Where is he?
Murderer!
You've betrayed us!
You should have stayed dead.
Dad?
Mark.
We need to talk.
No!
Someone's controlling you!
Dad!
Dad! Tell me how to stop them!
Mark...
Let my dad go!
Let him...
let him go.
Stop.
It's me, Mark.
It's just me.
This isn't how
I wanted to do this,
but I don't have a choice.
It's time for you to know
where I really come from.
I am from Viltrum,
but it's not the planet
I've told you about.
We have created
a perfect civilization,
but it took all of our strength,
determination,
and courage to get there.
In order for our people
to reach their full potential,
we had to remove the weak
from our society.
It was a long
and difficult process.
When it was over,
our population was cut in half,
but what emerged from the ashes
was unstoppable.
By the time I was born,
Viltrum was already
the greatest empire
in our galaxy.
We decided to make it
the only empire in our galaxy.
Once I was old enough,
I joined the war effort.
It was hard,
but I believe in our cause.
Some species resisted,
of course,
but no one could withstand us
for long.
Soon, our empire encompassed
thousands of planets.
But as our territory grew,
our forces were stretched thin
and our expansion stopped.
We needed a better,
more efficient way
to conquer worlds.
Our most trusted officers
were each given a planet
to weaken by themselves.
I was one of those lucky few.
I couldn't tell your mother
why I was here...
But that time's
come to an end...
And now we need
to get Earth ready
to join the Viltrum Empire.
Mark, this is good news.
We can finally do
what we were meant to do.
Be who we were meant to be.
You lied to me.
You couldn't know the truth...
Not until you had your powers.
Not until I was sure.
Sure of what?
Sure you were a Viltrumite.
So if I wasn't,
I'd just be
one more human to conquer?
No. This doesn't make any sense.
You love me.
You love Mom.
I know you do.
Do you have any idea
how long we live?
The older we get,
the slower we age.
Viltrumite DNA is so pure
you're nearly full-blooded.
You'll live
for thousands of years.
Do you understand
what that means?
Everyone you know and love
will be gone
before you even look 30.
It's not something
I want for you.
This isn't your world.
It's theirs.
But we can help them.
We can stop wars.
Eliminate hunger.
Give them medical technology
centuries ahead
of what they have now.
We've already been doing it.
If it wasn't for you and me,
this planet would be in flames.
All we have to do
is welcome Earth
into our empire.
I do love your mother.
But she's more like a...
a pet to me.
A pet?
This is the only way, Mark.
Don't touch me!
Calm down.
I will not calm down!
This is insane!
What do you think
is gonna happen?
That I'm gonna go enslave
my friends
for a bunch of aliens
I've never met?
This is my life!
These are my people!
We have a responsibility
to Viltrum...
I don't give a shit
about Viltrum.
And I don't care if I live
a fuckin' million years.
This is my home
and I won't let you destroy it!
You don't know
what you're saying.
And I can't let you interfere.
I know exactly what I'm saying.
So be it.
Do you really think
you can stop me?
Agh!
Map their trajectory.
I need to know
where they're going
before they get there.
Debbie, I'm so sorry
you had to listen to that.
They're going
to kill each other, Cecil!
You have to stop this.
We have them, sir.
They're slowing down
about 20 miles
southeast of Chicago.
Chicago?
They're in range.
Scramble our jets.
Sir? What could they do?
After everything else
we've thrown at Nolan?
Not much.
But at least
they're a distraction.
Maybe it'll give the kid
a chance
to think of something.
Holy fuck...
Okay, what do we do?
Do we go out there?
And do what?
We couldn't even
keep up with them.
No.
We follow Cecil's orders
and remain here.
This battle is beyond
our current capabilities.
Robot is...
Rudy's right.
We'll get our chance to help.
Eve! Oh Jesus Christ,
you're okay.
I'm fine.
What's happening
with Mark and Omni-Man?
Omni-Man's kicking
the shit out of him.
The world's gone
fucking nuts.
Indeed.
I truly hope
Mark lives up to his name.
To face his father and survive,
he'll need to be...
Don't do this!
It's not too late.
Yes, it is.
Target acquired.
Engaging.
Cecil wants to waste more time.
Look what they need to mimic
a fraction of our power.
As soon as they separate,
hit him
with everything you've got.
Roger that.
It's right to pity them, Mark,
but wrong to value them
over your own kind.
Now! Now! Now!
Direct hit.
Repeat, direct hit on Omni-Man.
- I got you.
- Chute won't deploy!
You won't need it.
Huh?
Ah, man!
Thank you.
Didn't think
I was gonna make it.
You almost killed him!
Instead, you saved him.
So much effort...
for what?
No!
Where was that other one?
He's on my six.
You killed him!
Now or in 50 years
when he's old.
What difference
does it make?
What difference?
He'd have a life!
Did seeing that man
lose his life disturb you?
Did it hurt?
Well, let's see
how you handle this.
Gretchen!
Mommy!
I've got you.
Don't move! Don't move!
Don't be scared, okay?
No, no!
How could you do this?
That was your fault.
Your stubbornness
against the inevitable
killed those people.
How many more
need to die, Mark?
It's up to you.
And what were they doing
with those
fragile little lives anyway?
Listen to what I'm saying.
You know in your heart
I'm right.
Right?
About how pathetic
and pointless humanity is?
Is Mom's life worthless?
In the grand scheme of things...
Yes.
Debbie.
How can you
say those things?
How can you say that about Mom?
Liar!
For the first time in your life,
I'm telling you the truth.
Let me...
I need to save them.
No.
Maybe this time,
you'll learn.
These people
are meaningless.
They're cavemen without us.
You're wrong!
I've seen you save people...
I've seen you almost die
to protect them.
Maybe you were a Viltrumite
when you came to Earth,
but you've changed!
You were happy here!
Sure. I was happy.
For a time.
But I'm loyal to Viltrum,
not this pathetic excuse
for a civilization.
Get off me!
You aren't listening, Mark.
My time here has been
a speck in the span of my life.
You don't know me.
I will burn this planet down
before I spend another minute
living among these animals.
Please.
I was wrong
to raise you as a human.
I should have
prepared you better.
Taught you more.
Your life has been
soft and painless.
You're a Viltrumite
in blood only.
Well, your true education
begins now.
Oh, my god. Mark...
Gear up.
We can't stop this fight,
but we can save lives.
Cecil's orders
were to stay here.
We don't care.
You're not a robot anymore,
remember?
Had enough yet?
I'll stop you.
I'm ready when you are.
You're doing this for nothing.
Being a part of the empire
will make Earth better
than it ever was.
And what if they resist?
That's why we're here.
To keep them from resisting.
To show them how wrong they are,
how pointless it is...
That they can be a part
of something bigger.
Or die.
I won't let you.
You want to die
for this planet?
Fine.
What's 17 more years?
I can always start again...
make another kid.
Yeah!
What are you doing?
If I have to watch this...
game,
I'd have a better view
from above.
You know you can't do that.
It's bad enough
you're standing over here
like a weirdo.
Come sit down.
This is a waste
of everyone's time.
There's so much more
I could be doing right now.
Go, Mark!
Oh! You're gonna miss it!
- Look at Mark.
- Strike one!
You and I, we made him.
He's ours.
When he feels joy, we feel joy.
See that look on his face?
How can you see that
and not feel the same way?
Strike two!
As we get older,
it's harder to feel that.
The weight of the world,
it bogs us down.
Nice one, honey!
But our children
remind us of the joys in life.
It brings us back,
shows us what life is all about.
This is humanity.
Yeah, yeah!
Get going, Mark!
Get going!
- C'mon, Mark!
- Go, Mark, go!
Go, Mark, go!
- C'mon, buddy, you can do it!
- Go, Mark! Go, Mark!
And safe!
Did you see, Dad?
Did you see?
Aw, that was amazing!
Yeah.
Yeah, I saw.
Dammit!
Why did you make me do this?
You're fighting so you can watch
everyone around you die!
Think, Mark!
You'll outlast
every fragile, insignificant
being on this planet.
You'll live to see this world
crumble to dust and blow away!
Everyone and everything
you know will be gone!
What will you have
after 500 years?
You, Dad.
I'd still have you.
Dad?
This is the scene
in downtown Chicago
as darkness falls
on the day the world changed.
Omni-Man and Invincible
touched down here
during their terrible battle.
The damage you can see
behind me
was done in a matter of minutes
before they carried
their fight elsewhere.
I can't begin
to explain the devastation,
the pain...
the loss.
It's like nothing...
...nothing I've ever seen.
And we're all asking
the same question...
how could someone
who promised to keep us safe,
to protect us
against any threat,
become that threat?
Without answers,
all we can do
is hold each other
as we pick up the pieces.
City planners estimate
that it will take weeks
to clear the area
before rebuilding can begin.
The cost in lives...
the cost in lives
is incalculable.
Thankfully,
the Guardians of the Globe
and Atom Eve are on the scene.
There's been no sign
of Omni-Man or Invincible
since yesterday.
In time, we hope to know
what ended this attack,
but for now,
we can be thankful
that the danger is behind us.
Don't try to talk.
You're going to be okay.
You're safe now.
It's all over.
Here. Drink.
I'm so proud of you.
I'll let you rest.
Debbie?
Sorry.
It's okay.
Look, I was...
I was wanting to...
Look, if this is too much,
just say so.
If it were me,
it would ease my mind
to know that
things are taken care of, so...
Just get on with it, Cecil.
Since we want to preserve
Omni-Man's secret identity
to keep you and Mark safe,
Nolan Grayson officially died
when the house across the street
exploded from a gas leak.
Now, Nolan's travel books
always sold well,
but sales will see
a significant spike
after his death,
so you and Mark
will be fine for money.
And don't be alarmed
if you see yourself and Mark
on the news.
We sent proxies to the funeral
so your lives can go back
to some kind of normal
once Mark's healed up.
Normal?
Look, I...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean...
What I meant was...
No. I'm sorry.
This is all very kind.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Nolan was doing
everything under my nose
and I never saw it.
I wouldn't be able
to live with myself
if I didn't make things
as right as they can be.
Man.
We haven't earned it yet.
Seriously?
Fuck off.
I said, stop!
Now we look like a team.
♪ The hope outweighs
all my sorrow ♪
♪ I believe ♪
♪ And the vast, open sky
shows them all ♪
♪ What I could be ♪
♪ And the colors
drift from you ♪
♪ Into me ♪
♪ And the wonder
of the moment ♪
♪ Sticks to me ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ And the colors
drift from you ♪
♪ Into me ♪
♪ And the wonder
of the moment ♪
♪ Rescued me ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
Oh...
Hey, William.
Oh, um, hey, Eve.
Uh...
Have you heard from Mark?
Not since that stuff
between him and his dad
on the news.
I'm really worried tha...
Oh, shit!
Wait a minute.
You know he's Invincible?
Oh, man.
You know, too?
Oh, thank god!
I thought I blew it.
You... you think he's okay?
I don't know.
Hmm.
That was a hell of thing
you did there, kid.
I, um... I thought
it might have been a dream...
I wish it were.
You've been drifting
in and out
for almost two weeks,
but my guys
got you patched up good.
We'll let you out
in a day or two.
I saw my dad fly away.
Where'd he go?
Get your rest, kid.
We'll talk later.
Hey. Wait.
Wait!
Aren't you going to tell me
what happened?
- That depends.
- On what?
On if you still want
to be a hero or not.
I don't know.
Come with me.
I wanted to tell you
that your mother heard
everything that your dad said,
so you don't have to go
through the trouble
of explaining this whole ordeal.
What? She heard everything?
How could you do that?
Don't you think
she deserves to know the truth?
Yeah, but...
Your mother knew
he killed the Guardians,
but she was holding out hope
there was a good reason for it.
So was I.
Better for her to know
everything about your father.
Maybe you're right.
Wait a minute.
Where are we?
Oh,
sorry.
Lights.
Whoa!
That's enough.
Lights.
What? What the hell
just happened?
Where'd all that go?
The water America drinks
so conveniently from their taps
is laced with a chemical
that inhibits the ability
to see
certain frequencies of light.
Those frequencies
are used in this room.
So it's all just invisible?
You and everyone else
in America
do not have the ability
to see the things in this room.
You'd be surprised
how often we use this.
Wild.
To answer your question,
we monitored your father
until he left our solar system.
He didn't change trajectory,
so he's going somewhere
pretty damn far away.
Which means...
we, um...
we need a replacement.
No.
Not now. Not yet.
Your dad didn't leave me
with a lot of options, Mark.
If I can't call on you...
well, there's not really a list
past the Guardians of the Globe.
I know...
I'm sorry.
It's just...
it's too much.
I shouldn't have
brought this up so soon.
Let's get you and your mother
home first.
We fixed the house.
Talked to your school
and Debbie's work.
There's even a headstone
in the cemetery...
not that you'd want to visit it.
If either of you
need anything else,
you know how to reach me.
Thanks, Cecil.
Much better.
I'm going to go
lie down for a bit.
Okay, Mom.
Guess who's
finally getting his powers.
Oh, that's great, son,
just great!
If you really want to do
what I do,
you have to be prepared
for anything.
Dad!
Ow! Ribs.
I'm scared, Dad.
What if I can't do this?
This is the beginning
of a long journey
for you and me.
Along the way,
you're going to need
to do things
you don't want to do,
or might not think you can do.
You're a Viltrumite.
We have responsibilities...
...that normal humans don't.
I want to do what you do!
I want to be just like you.
You will be, son.
You will be.
Mom!
I'm going to order
something for dinner.
Want to get a pizza?
Mark!
Whoa. Uh...
Does this mean... uh?
I mean, if you want.
But what about...
Looks like I wasn't
the only person being lied to.
You know Omni-Man is my...
They said your dad was killed
when a gas line
blew up across the street.
Not that hard
to figure it out from there.
Detective Amber,
ready to help out
on any tough cases that come up.
Are you...
I know you're not okay,
but do you want
to talk about it?
Yeah.
I think I do.
Mark!
Oh, man, it's so good
to see you're all right.
I mean, after everything
on the TV
about you and Omniiii...
Uh, hey, Amber.
Uh, um...
She knows about my dad.
Oh, okay.
They know?
You guys want to, uh...
Let's go out.
We're not open!
How did you get...
Debbie.
How are you holding up?
Scratch that.
Stupid question.
What can I do for you?
I spent so much time
thinking about
if Nolan had killed
the Guardians...
and why he would have done it...
I...
I didn't think about
what would happen afterwards.
Where it would leave me...
and Mark.
After everything
Nolan said and did...
I still can't believe it.
I can't believe
our time together was a lie.
I wish he'd come back.
Me too.
Pour me one of those.
I've only got
the one glass.
I don't care. Pour.
How's your mom taking it?
About as badly
as you'd expect.
Mark, I am so sorry.
I don't know what to say.
It's like I'm hollow inside.
Nothing seems real.
We don't have to do this here.
No.
It's okay.
I just needed
to get out of the house.
But can we...
talk about something else?
We can try,
but it's literally
all anyone is talking about
in the whole world.
Okay.
Sorry.
New topic.
Uh... Huh.
Hold on.
Hello?
I need you. Now. Hurry.
Sorry, I'll be right back.
What is it?
I know you've said
you don't want to do this.
Someone's flying towards Earth
from deep space.
We're still trying
to figure out who it is,
but...
You know about
Mark and Omni-Man now,
so you might as well
know about me.
I met Mark in costume
before I realized
we went to the same school.
I'm, um...
well, I'm Atom Eve.
What?
Oh, my god, I see it now!
You can make
doubles of yourself!
No! That's Dupli-Kate.
I'm the pink one.
Oh, right.
Of course.
Invincible!
Oh...
it's just you.
Oh, thank heavens!
I-I thought I was too late!
I have to warn you!
Warn me?
When I returned
to the Coalition of Planets
to tell them I'd been going
to Earth instead of Urath,
they lost their minds!
Earth is off limits...
there's a Viltrumite
living on your planet!
Oh. That.
Wait... What?
You already know?
Uh... yeah.
I don't understand.
Grab a seat.
This may take a while.
So...
you're a Viltrumite?
But you don't work for them?
And your dad tried
to take over the planet
but then left?
He just left?
That's nuts, man.
Yeah.
As far as we can tell,
my dad is just gone.
That is super weird
for a Viltrumite.
They don't just give up.
They're relentless.
They destroyed my world
when my people
rebelled against them.
They blew up our planet
rather than lose it.
Jesus...
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
From the sounds of it,
I'm the one
who should be apologizing.
If I'd checked
my orders properly,
I would've seen
that Earth was flagged
for Viltrumite takeover.
I could have warned you.
I would have just
gone to my dad
and told him everything.
Who knows
what would have happened then?
I can't imagine
what you're going through.
Literally.
Like, I have no concept of it.
With my home world gone,
my people had to create
breeding camps
just to stop us
from going extinct.
I've never even
met my father.
After the last few days,
I'm jealous.
The Coalition of Planets
will want to hear about you.
A power struggle's brewing
in the farthest reaches
of space.
What kind of
power struggle?
The Coalition is trying
to unite enough worlds
to stop the Viltrumite empire.
The thing is...
no one's even heard of
a Viltrumite
abandoning their post.
It's insane.
It just doesn't happen.
This could be the advantage
we've been looking for.
Sure.
Let me know if I can do
anything to help.
I don't get
why you're smiling?
Just thinking about
everything I've been through.
How huge it all feels.
But the fact it's just
a small part of something
much larger
makes it all seem more...
manageable.
I don't know.
But it helps.
Sorry to rain on your parade.
That happens on Earth, right?
Anyway, once they find out
your father took off,
the Viltrumites
are gonna come for you.
Trust me, when they set
their sights on a planet,
they don't give up
without a fight.
I'll be ready.
I hope so.
What's the plan
in the meantime?
♪ Do what I want
'cause I can ♪
♪ And if I don't
because I wanna ♪
♪ Be ignored by the stiff
and the bored ♪
♪ Because I'm gonna ♪
♪ Hate to say I told you so ♪
♪ All right! ♪
♪ Come on! ♪
Yeah!
♪ I do believe
I told you so... ♪
♪ Now it's all out
and you knew ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanted to ♪
♪ No need for me to wait ♪
♪ Because I wanna ♪
♪ No need two, three, too late ♪
♪ Because I'm gonna ♪
♪ Hate to say I told you so ♪
♪ All right! ♪
♪ Come on! ♪
♪ I do believe
I told you so ♪
Finish high school, I guess.
Oh, all right. Good.
Sounds good.
What is high school?
♪ Now it's all out
and you knew ♪
♪ 'Cause I wanted to ♪
♪ Turn my back on the rot ♪
♪ That's been planning
the plot ♪
♪ Because I'm gonna ♪
♪ No need for me to wait ♪
♪ Because I wanna ♪
♪ No need two, three, too late ♪
♪ Because I'm gonna ♪
♪ Hate to say I told you so ♪
♪ All right! ♪
♪ Ask me once
I'll answer twice ♪
♪ 'Cause all I know I'll tell ♪
♪ Because I wanna ♪
♪ Sound device and lots of ice ♪
♪ I'll spell my name out loud ♪
♪ Because I wanna! ♪
♪ Oh, yeah! ♪