Shit.
Look at that place.
Language.
Sorry.
I mean, it's impressive,
but, like, who needs
that many rooms?
It's not about rooms.
It's about power.
That building has one purpose.
To say, "I'm the Queen,
and you are my subjects."
Huh.
You think so?
The Queen might look
like a nice old lady,
but she comes from
a long line of tyrants
who all thought they were
better than the rest of us.
Dad!
I didn't know
they had Burger Marts here.
You called me Dad.
Clear.
Go, go, go!
Get in there!
One team per casualty!
- Move it!
- Jesus Christ.
What the hell happened here?
Applying aqueous sealant.
Is that part of her brain?
It's the Green Ghost!
Did you find all the pieces?
I used
to worship this guy as a kid.
Get those on ice.
Cut in the neck now.
Watch out.
Sometimes, it affects
the spinal...
Beginning nano-suscitation.
Locking in neural stabilizer.
Omni-Man's alive!
Get out of the way!
Hurry up!
It's all we can do here.
Get ready for transport.
Go, go, go!
Careful.
Don't bump her.
Never seen anything like this.
Goddammit!
Hey, Mom.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just missing your dad.
He didn't come home last night.
Mom, stop worrying.
He probably got buried
under a mountain again
or something.
Well, it wouldn't be
the first time.
Don't be late for school.
Nolan's receiving
the absolute pinnacle of care.
As the Global Defense Agency,
we have access
to medical technology
far beyond any normal hospital.
Whoa...
Ah, that's one of
our threat-response teams.
They're able to get anywhere...
We're not in the mood
for the tour, Donald.
Sorry, Debbie.
My dad never mentioned
you guys.
That's the idea.
We work with superheroes
like your father
to keep the world safe.
Who knows, maybe someday,
we'll even work with...
Oh, my god, Nolan!
Dad!
He's gonna be okay, right?
We... hope so,
and our doctors
are doing their best,
but we don't get a lot
of Viltrumites in here.
Who did this?
We have no idea.
Not yet, anyway,
but we'll find out,
and when we do,
they're gonna look
a hell of a lot worse
than your dad right over there.
Cecil Steadman.
Director of the GDA.
Deborah,
I'm so sorry.
Cecil,
you've got a lot of nerve.
Someone murdered the Guardians
of the Globe last night.
Oh, my god.
All of them.
Tore 'em limb from limb.
Now, we tried like hell
to bring 'em back,
but Nolan was
the only survivor.
How is that even possible?
We don't know yet.
We also don't know why
your dad was at Guardians' HQ.
Now, working theory is,
whoever killed the Guardians
lured him there,
tried to wipe 'em
all out at once.
- Why?
Well, that's the easy part.
There isn't
a super-villain alive
who doesn't want Omni-Man
and the Guardians
six feet under.
Now, we're keeping this
all hush-hush for now,
but news will break.
I wanted you and Mark
to know first.
Cold towels,
and ice water,
and have a cot
brought in here for me.
Deborah, we've got
the best-trained...
I've patched Nolan up
for 20 years, Cecil.
I am not leaving.
Of-of course, Debbie.
Sir...
There's some kind of attack
happening downtown, it seems.
Numerous contacts.
Heavy weaponry.
Multiple casualties.
Now?
We're a little understaffed
in the hero department.
Holy shit.
Get it together, Mark.
Get it together.
Get in there.
Stop!
Get away from those people!
Oh, shit.
Get it together.
Help me.
No!
It's okay.
It's okay, I'm here.
Are you hurt?
Brax moy!
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my god...
Huh?
I don't know who you are,
but it's time to go.
Eve, two and a half
seconds after this sentence,
three enemy tanks will align
50 degrees to your right.
I got it.
Rex...
civilians in danger
to your left.
Uh, yeah,
I got eyes, too, Robot.
Dupli-Kate...
Keep doing what you are doing.
You! Get her to a hospital!
We can handle this.
You're Atom Eve...
What?
Just go!
Admirable intention, Eve,
but I am not positive
we can handle this.
Ha! Huh...
Oh.
Uh, guys?
I'm down to pocket change here.
They're killing me
faster than I can keep up.
We gave people time to escape.
That's what matters.
Uh, no.
Me living is what matters.
Then I have bad news.
Ah!
I don't know
what just happened,
but I think I speak
for everyone here
when I say
I never want it to happen
ever again!
Y'ah!
Indeed.
Help!
Anyone!
I need help!
Freeze.
She needs a doctor!
- He's covered in blood.
- Come on!
Give her to us.
Clamp that vein
and get a drip started.
- Prep operating room six.
- Yes, doctor.
He's clear.
Mark!
I tried my best.
I tried to be like Dad.
It's okay.
Hey!
Hey...
Watch it!
Dick...
Hey, Mark.
Mark.
Mark!
Whoa.
Are you okay?
My dad, um...
he got attacked.
What?
You're kidding.
Oh, god, you're not kidding.
Is-Is he okay?
What happened?
He's in the hospital.
They're doing, uh...
They're doing their best,
but it's...
It's messed up, William.
He's really hurt.
Jesus, Mark.
I'm so sorry.
Did they catch who did it?
No, not yet.
Speaking as someone
who's been attacked
in this stupid city,
I'm here for you.
Whatever you need.
You wanna talk, I'll listen.
You and Debbie need a lasagna,
I make a good one.
Actually, I make a great one.
Eve Wilkins...
What?
Um...
Yeah, that's her.
I need to talk to her.
You and all the other
straight boys
in a ten-mile radius.
Good luck with that,
and didn't you just get
your ass kicked last week
for Amber Bennett?
Eve?
Hi, uh...
Oh, hey.
Mark, right?
Grayson, yeah.
Um...
thanks for saving
my butt back there.
Y-Yesterday, I mean.
Yesterday? Oh.
Oh!
That was you?
In the blue and the yellow?
Yeah.
That was me.
I'm, um...
Invincible.
God, that sounds dumb
when I say it like that.
It sounds a little
optimistic maybe.
I'm Atom Eve,
but the rest of the team
just calls me Eve.
So does everyone else.
Right, since it's
kind of a normal name,
and not something like...
Invincible?
Invincible, yeah.
Do you want to talk
about yesterday?
You look like you need
to talk about yesterday.
I heard he just
let Todd hit him.
Like 20 times.
He didn't flinch
or anything.
Todd got so freaked out
he stayed home
for three days.
Are you talking about
Mark Grayson?
Duh. Of course, Amber.
You're the reason
Todd beat him up again.
I never
recognized you before.
No one does.
It's a psychology thing.
If you don't expect to see
a superhero in your school,
you don't see a superhero
in your school.
Hmm.
I even follow Teen Team
on Instagram.
That's us.
Everyone's fourth favorite
superhero team.
I like you guys way better
than Fight Force.
Oh, we're definitely
better than Fight Force.
Those guys are the worst.
They got their asses kicked
by the Lizard League last year.
Oh, I remember
seeing that on TV.
So...
you're new to this, right?
Uh... I just got my powers.
That was my first big fight.
Ah, okay.
Explains a lot.
Still, not bad for a rookie.
Are you kidding?
I froze out there.
People got hurt.
People escaped because of you,
and everyone freezes
their first time.
I used to throw up
before every fight.
Barf my guts out.
Really?
Like a fire hydrant.
You'll get used to it.
The fights, not the barfing.
Ah...
I just...
It wasn't what I expected.
I figured I'd punch some aliens,
and they'd go home.
It's not how it looks on TV.
No shit.
Thanks.
I charge 250 an hour.
Now I'm kidding.
You are new at this.
Why don't you come by
and meet the Team after school?
Teen Team?
I dunno...
I heard they were only
everyone's fourth favorite.
Meet me out front
after class, Invincible.
You kids did good, Robot.
Thank you, Cecil.
It's an honor to assist
the Global Defense Agency.
Though your use
of the term "kids"
might be considered
condescending.
But a victory?
No.
Do you know how many people
died here yesterday?
338.
338...
and it only stopped there
because whoever the hell
those assholes were, ran away.
- The Flaxans.
- What?
They call themselves
the Flaxans.
I reverse-engineered
their language
using recordings
from the battle.
Any idea why they left
just when they were
kicking our asses?
I have six ideas...
...but I believe that
narrows it down to one.
Oxidized and corroded.
For an alloy like this,
that should take years.
Time runs faster
wherever they come from.
They ran off because they...
Because they were dying
of old age.
Huh.
Well, if they come back,
maybe I'll just
evacuate the area
and wait till they get cancer.
How did that new kid do?
Invincible?
He has promise,
but he seems unprepared
for the more realistic aspects
of super-herodom.
Well, he'd better toughen up.
We're gonna need his help.
Why?
From one giant shitshow
to another.
Give me some good news, Donald.
Whoever did this cut the power
and the backup.
They killed the cameras
and the security systems.
Forensics, frankly, is stumped.
I told them to start over
and try harder.
That's not good news.
That's not good news at all!
I asked you
for some good news, Donald!
Get the hell out.
Everyone.
Come on, you heard the director.
Move it!
Come on out.
I know you're there.
Wasn't hiding.
Sir, who the hell...
Damien Darkblood,
demon detective.
Huh...
Seven superheroes murdered.
Strongest man on the planet
almost dead.
No suspects. No leads.
How does he...
I don't know.
Demon magic or something.
If you're asking
if we need your help...
Wasn't asking.
Fine. Knock yourself out.
Help us solve the case,
oh, Great-horned Holmes.
Sir... are you sure?
You got a problem
with the demon?
I thought you were
an atheist, Donald.
Th-theoretically.
Hey.
I heard you took
a few on the chin
for me again.
Oh, hey, Amber.
Uh, yeah, but don't worry,
I've got this amazing
new strategy
for dealing with Todd.
I let him hit me
until he gets bored
and goes home.
Hmm... nice.
He'll never see it coming.
Unfortunately,
neither will your face.
Eh, people always told me
I was too pretty anyway.
I gotta run.
Catch you later?
Ready?
Try to keep up.
Eve?
Eve!
Whoa! Shit!
Oof!
Okay.
Let's try this again.
Follow me.
Now what?
Oh!
Cool.
Ha!
Babe.
Oh, hey!
It's the iceman.
Rex...
Couldn't have won
that fight without you.
Oh! Except we did.
They got old.
And ran away.
Still counts.
Welcome, Invincible.
My name is Robot.
Apologies for Rex Splode.
He's...
Unbelievably awesome.
Incorrigible.
And rude.
And bored of this.
I'm Dupli-Kate.
Invincible.
Which one of you do I
look at when we talk?
Hey, Robot,
find anything at the site?
The Flaxans
come from a dimension
with a faster temporal rate.
As a result,
the tachyons they emit
spin more rapidly than our own.
I've created this detector
to warn us if they return.
Ah, because we almost
missed all the explosions
and the screaming and the chaos.
It should give us
a few minutes of early warning.
Cecil and the GDA
have also requested
to call on us
for any possible emergencies.
Since the Guardians
are apparently indisposed,
Invincible, may we count on you
in the future?
You sure you want my help?
Yeah, I mean, of course.
Just text me, I guess.
Oh, right, you need my number.
I know you don't like
teams much,
but they were all pretty cool.
Except Rex Splode.
I do not know
what that guy's problem is.
I think he and Eve
are a thing maybe.
Who's Eve?
Uh...
No one.
Just-just a friend.
Mm-hmm.
Did you find the dinners
in the freezer?
Yeah.
Thanks, Mom.
Oh, Mark, I'm sorry.
I've been so focused on your dad
that I've forgotten about you.
Are you okay?
Donald said you saved
a lot of lives.
Yeah. It was just, um...
harder than I thought.
Dad didn't talk about this part
of being a superhero.
Your dad's good at
a lot of things.
Talking about his feelings
isn't one of them...
but we can talk.
Is, uh...
is she okay?
Her name's Maya.
Doesn't she have
any family?
We've contacted them, yes,
but this is a secure facility.
She's not strong enough
for us to transfer her
to a normal hospital.
But she'll be okay?
Well, it's too soon to tell,
but I hope so.
Whoo!
Is this supposed to be
doing that?
Huh?
We're just friends.
Will you stop saying that?
It's like you're trying to jinx
any chance you have
of dating Eve.
A day ago,
you said I had no chance!
That was before
everyone saw you
leave school
with her yesterday.
Everyone saw that?
It doesn't matter.
She already has a boyfriend.
So?
You can be more awesome than him
and take his place.
That's how dating works!
Why are you
so intimidated by her?
Other than she's amazing
and you're kinda basic?
Thanks for that, William.
I gotta go.
Go?
Go where?
You know what, I don't care.
It's probably somewhere
you'll be alone forever.
Is Mark dating Eve Wilkins?
I wish!
I-I mean, no.
Definitely not.
She's got a boyfriend.
He is super available.
Want his number?
I'll write it down for you.
Uh, where are you guys
coming from?
Um, we go to the same
high-school, Rex.
Oh, you do, do you?
Um, yeah, we do.
Must be nice.
You know who never
got to go to high school?
Me.
We know.
It shows.
I'd appreciate
everyone's attention
on the matter at hand.
Guess who's back.
They're not getting old, Robot.
Why aren't they getting old?
They seem to have discovered
a way to resist
our time stream.
In three days?
Three days for us.
Decades for them.
Who cares?
I bet their bones still break.
So do ours!
Ready for this?
Yeah.
I think so.
Ah!
Orep udea!
Hey, don't do that!
Run!
Whew...
Y'ah!
Ah!
Ugh!
Xopa moy.
They seem...
to have spent
their time wisely.
Eve!
No, don't!
Don't. Don't! No!
I said, no!
Brax moy!
Invincible!
Eve!
You okay?
The wristbands protect them
from our timestream.
Destroy their wristbands.
What?
All of them?
Y'ah!
49,000 kilohertz.
Keep them off meeee...
♪ eeeeee... ♪
Right back 'atcha, buddy.
Way to go psycho there,
Invincible.
I take back everything
I said about you before,
and I said a lot.
I don't know what happened.
I got mad... I guess?
Don't get me wrong,
that was amazing,
but also the scariest thing
I've ever seen.
Just don't ever
point that at me, okay?
Don't listen to Rex.
You did great.
That's what I said, Eve.
God, my back.
Can I get a massage?
Anybody?
Just a little rub?
Everything okay?
I gotta go.
Oh, no, that's fine.
We'll handle the clean-up.
Asshole!
Oh!
Mark!
- Hey, son.
- Dad!
Ow!
Ribs...
Careful!
You're going to put him
in a coma again.
You're okay!
No, he's not,
but he is okay enough
to come home.
Mom says you've been keeping
the planet safe for me.
Mom's exaggerating.
Tell me everything.
What hospital
did they move Maya to?
No, they said she'd recover.
It's part of the job.
Come on, let's go home.
I'm dying for some real food.
Hey, I need my costume back.
I don't care how torn up it is.
It's classified,
and I want it back.
Go get it.
Now.
Where are
the Guardians of the Globe?
There's been no sign
of the iconic heroes
for over a week,
leaving the local champions
to pick up the slack.
It's like
you're not even trying.
And now you're trying too hard.
Slow down.
Don't hit me where I am,
hit me where I'm going...
Thanks for the tip.
You know, you have to be able
to take a hit, too.
Nolan!
Oh, great.
We picked this up
near Mars an hour ago.
Moving fast.
He's back.
15 minutes
till he's breathing our air.
I wouldn't ask, Nolan,
but with the Guardians gone...
I'll stop him.
Who's he?
Nolan's been home a week,
and you want to send him
to space?
No. No way.
He doesn't work for you.
Sweetie...
There's no one else, Debbie.
I'll go.
- Sweetie...
- I said, no.
You're still injured.
I'll go.
Okay.
- What?
- Why not?
He's not that tough.
Mark can take him.
Oh, wonderful.
That's your solution?
Could you define
"not that tough"?
Just knock some sense
into the guy
and throw him
back where he came from.
Easy.
How do I breathe in space?
That's the neat thing.
You don't.
12 minutes.
Okay...
Hey, you're early!
And you shaved your mustache.
Stay away from my planet!
Not bad,
but if you're trying
to tackle me into something,
your moon is that way!
Why can I hear you in my head?
Where else
do you keep your brain?
That's what you call
protecting your planet?
I am sad for your people!
Are you sure you're the same guy
I fought here three years ago?
What? No, I'm not the same guy!
Well, sucks to be you then.
Ah, my eye!
Really?
- You tried this already.
- Huh?
Ha!
Maybe you'll do after all.
What are you talking about?
Wait! Stop! I...
Hold on, I just wanna...
I wanna talk!
Are you using your time out?
I get a time out?
Why do I get a time out?
Hey, I didn't invent the rules.
What rules?
I don't even know who you are!
Oh. You don't?
All right, um...
I'm an evaluation officer
for the Coalition of Planets.
I drop by little dirtballs
like yours
to make sure there's someone
capable of defending them
against, you know,
planet-conquering monsters,
things of that nature.
I literally have no idea
what any of that means.
Well, I don't know
what to tell you, man.
Your planet signed up
for the program.
See?
Request from Urath
for evaluation.
Urath!
This is Earth!
Earth?
Yes!
Not Urath?
No.
Is that with an "E"
or a "U"?
"E"!
Oh, I'm in so much trouble.
Well, thanks
for letting me know.
I'm Allen, by the way.
Invincible.
Oh, yeah?
A little optimistic, isn't it?
Yeah, I know.
I just fought you,
and I think
you're quite "vincible."
Okay, well, as long as
I don't get fired,
I'll see you around, Invincible.
Sorry about all the...
you know.
What the hell was that?
Wow.
Cool.
Before I go...
I already told you
everything I remember.
Right.
Right, just go over it
for me one more time.
I got a distress call
from the Guardians,
but when I arrived,
everything seemed fine.
Then the lights went out
and someone attacked me.
I fought with them
until I passed out.
Woke up in your hospital.
That's it.
That's it?
Hmm.
Must have been
a pretty tough bastard
to take you down.
I've never seen you lose
like that before.
Yeah.
Do you have any leads yet?
Someone thinks
they're too clever for us.
They all think that at first.
Oh, my God!
Ow!
Oh, great.
Excuse you.
Look, Todd.
Why don't we just...
Shut it, Grayson!
- I'm sorry.
- What?
I'm sorry I kicked your ass.
I don't know
what you're saying.
I'm sorry
I kicked your ass, okay?
Oh.
Thanks, I guess?
Amber Bennett
also wants to know
- if you'd like her number.
- What?
Do you want Amber's
phone number, nerd!
Yes, but why are you...
Because she found
some old photos of me, okay?
Photos she said she'd delete
if I did this one stupid thing,
and then never
talked to you again.
There.
Have a crappy life with her.
You both suck.
Photos of what, Todd?
Don't push your luck, Grayson.
Amber?
I-I mean, uh, hello?
Brax moy!
I have bad news.
Oh!
Robot's got bad news, everybody.
Did ya hear that?
Hey, Robot,
what's the bad news?
There are too many of them,
their technology
has advanced too far,
and they've rendered themselves
immune to our time stream.
We should consider
the city lost.
I will contact Cecil
and suggest a nuclear response.
What? No!
No way!
We're not nuking anyone, Robot,
and we're not giving up.
What are we, Fight Force?
I love you, man,
but sometimes,
you've got a screw loose.
I don't use screws.
My fastenings are all
magnetic interlocks.
Oh!
Invincible!
Ah!
Help.
Die.
Are you okay, Mark?
My turn.
H'ah!
Juti urec!
Laji moy!
Dad!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Omni-Man's your dad?
What happened?
Dad saved us from the Flaxans...
but he went into
one of their portals.
Oh.
So he'll be late for dinner?
I was worried before
because I've never seen
your father so badly hurt,
but taking on aliens
in another dimension?
That's just Tuesday.
I'm sure he's explaining nicely
why they should leave us alone.
You don't seem to understand.
Earth isn't yours to conquer.
I need a shower.
Dad!
I'm-I'm at a loss
for how to report this,
but the Guardians of the Globe
are dead.
Get an extraction team
out there now.
Tell the French President
we have it covered.
I need the room.
Now!
Well? Enlighten me.
Know one thing for sure.
No one else at scene of murders.
Only Guardians.
Omni-Man.
Which means killer must be
one of them.
One of them?
There's a hundred super-villains
who don't leave a trace.
Who turn into smoke,
or living electricity,
or only exist in dreams.
I know.
You don't listen to me.
You listen!
Now, you mention
your idiotic thoughts to anyone,
and I mean anybody,
I'll make sure they're
the last thoughts you ever have.
You understand me?
Now, get out.
Get out!
Before I send you
back to hell myself.
Blind old man.
Put an A-6 surveillance team
on the Graysons.
Sir?
The killer's
still out there, Donald.
Might decide
to finish the job.